[
    {
        "story_id": "./cnn/stories/9e141ebc1c06d483bf85f4e5c8b3c7bc2d00ea2f.story",
        "story_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.\n\nThe base, in southern Turkey near Syria, is a major resupply center for U.S. operations in Iraq and elsewhere in the Mideast and Asia.\n\nThe Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\n\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \"genocide\" label.\n\nThe House Foreign Affairs Committee last week adopted the nonbinding resolution. House Speaker Nancy Pelosi said she would bring the measure to a vote of the full House sometime next month. But the Bush administration urged Congress to drop the issue, and some leading Democrats urged Pelosi not to bring it to the floor.\n\nMajority Leader Steny Hoyer signaled Tuesday that the vote might be put off.\n\n\"I said I thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here,\" said Hoyer of Maryland. \"I have not changed on that, although I would be less than candid to say that there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions. We will have to determine where everybody is.\"\n\nDemocratic Rep. Ike Skelton, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, announced his opposition to the resolution last week.\n\nAnd Democratic Reps. Alcee Hastings of Florida and John Tanner of Tennessee, both members of the U.S. House delegation to NATO, urged Pelosi to reconsider in a letter released Tuesday.\n\n\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\" they wrote.\n\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \"a broad range of options\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.\n\n\"We're confident that we'll find ways to do that,\" Ham told reporters at the Pentagon. \"There's likely to be some increased cost and some other implications for that, and obviously we'd prefer to maintain the access that we have.\"\n\nDefense Secretary Robert Gates echoed lawmakers' concerns last week.\n\n\"About 70 percent of all air cargo going into Iraq goes through Turkey. ... About a third of the fuel that they consume goes through Turkey or comes from Turkey,\" Gates said.\n\nHe also said that 95 percent of the Mine-Resistant Ambush-Protective vehicles, or MRAPs, being deployed in Iraq are flown through Turkey. The vehicles are built to withstand roadside bombs.  See Incirlik's key location Â»\n\nThe U.S. military issued a \"warning order\" a few days ago to ensure that alternative air crews, planes, fuel and routes are lined up if Turkey stops or restricts U.S. access to Incirlik, a source said.\n\nJordan and Kuwait are among the alternatives the United States is considering.\n\nSome fear pursuit of the resolution would also embolden the Turks to attack Kurdish rebels in northern Iraq which could further complicate Iraqi stability, U.S. officials said.\n\nIncirlik offers 10,000- and 9,000-foot runways and 57 hardened aircraft shelters, according Globalsecurity.org, a source of background information about military issues.\n\nGlobalsecurity said Incirlik has become a hub for cargo shipments to Iraq, taking over for Rhein-Main Air Base in Germany because it is closer to Iraq, reducing the strain on troops and aircraft. E-mail to a friend\n\nCNN's Barbara Starr and Deirdre Walsh contributed to this report.",
        "questions": [
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 1919,
                "question": "What says a number of Dems are revisiting?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1385:1404|1380:1404|1234:1262,1385:1404|1477:1494,1501:1519,1530:1551",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1385:1404\": 1, \"1234:1262\": 1, \"1530:1551\": 1}",
                "para_text": "Majority Leader Steny Hoyer signaled Tuesday that the vote might be put off.\n\n\"I said I thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here,\" said Hoyer of Maryland. \"I have not changed on that, although I would be less than candid to say that there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions. We will have to determine where everybody is.\"\n\nDemocratic Rep. Ike Skelton, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, announced his opposition to the resolution last week.",
                "pred_ans": "their own positions",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 6014,
                "question": "Where is the key supply for the military?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "411:429|482:523|3716:3725|686:691",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"3716:3725\": 1, \"411:429\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\n\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \"genocide\" label.",
                "pred_ans": "incirlik",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 6435,
                "question": "What is the genocide?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\n\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \"genocide\" label.",
                "pred_ans": "killings of armenians",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 10287,
                "question": "Who is revisiting their positions?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1492:1511|1492:1511",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Majority Leader Steny Hoyer signaled Tuesday that the vote might be put off.\n\n\"I said I thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here,\" said Hoyer of Maryland. \"I have not changed on that, although I would be less than candid to say that there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions. We will have to determine where everybody is.\"\n\nDemocratic Rep. Ike Skelton, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, announced his opposition to the resolution last week.",
                "pred_ans": "a number of people who are revisiting their own positions",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 13536,
                "question": "what did house resolution calls?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "107:167|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 1, \"bad_question\": 1, \"107:167\": 1}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "genocide",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 13628,
                "question": "What did the Majority Leader say?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1284:1311|1312:1380,1404:1473,1477:1598|1312:1380,1404:1473,1477:1598",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Majority Leader Steny Hoyer signaled Tuesday that the vote might be put off.\n\n\"I said I thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here,\" said Hoyer of Maryland. \"I have not changed on that, although I would be less than candid to say that there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions. We will have to determine where everybody is.\"\n\nDemocratic Rep. Ike Skelton, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, announced his opposition to the resolution last week.",
                "pred_ans": "i said i thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 23563,
                "question": "Which air base is Key for U.S. military's supply of Iraq mission?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "193:202|1996:2005|1996:2005",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\" they wrote.\n\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \"a broad range of options\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.",
                "pred_ans": "incirlik air base",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 28694,
                "question": "What resolution is Turkey upset about?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "81:87|116:152,154:167,81:87,98:107|116:152,154:167,98:107|330:377",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 1, \"330:377\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "the resolution calling the killing of armenians by ottoman turks genocide",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 29068,
                "question": "Who is upset about genocide resolution?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "240:248|25:35|240:248,291:300|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"240:248\": 2, \"none\": 1}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "democrats",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 34525,
                "question": "What air base is a key point for US military supply?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "193:202,214:230|1996:2005|193:202,411:420|1996:2005",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"193:202\": 1, \"none\": 1, \"1996:2005\": 1}",
                "para_text": "The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\n\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \"genocide\" label.",
                "pred_ans": "incirlik",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 37797,
                "question": "Who is upset about World War I \"genocide\" resolution in Congress?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1599:1680,1739:1890,1893:1920|240:248|1615:1628,1756:1771,1786:1798|25:35",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1599:1680\": 2, \"25:35\": 1}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "democrats",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 39376,
                "question": "Who is supplying the U.S. military?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "618:631|2820:2829|504:511|193:211",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"2820:2829\": 1, \"618:631\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\n\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \"genocide\" label.",
                "pred_ans": "turkey",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 39503,
                "question": "What air base is a key point of US military supply?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "193:202|411:420|193:202",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\" they wrote.\n\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \"a broad range of options\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.",
                "pred_ans": "incirlik air base",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 46073,
                "question": "what is turkey upset about?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "116:152,154:167|303:377|300:318|287:377",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"303:377\": 1, \"300:318\": 1, \"116:152\": 1}",
                "para_text": "Defense Secretary Robert Gates echoed lawmakers' concerns last week.\n\n\"About 70 percent of all air cargo going into Iraq goes through Turkey. ... About a third of the fuel that they consume goes through Turkey or comes from Turkey,\" Gates said.\n\nHe also said that 95 percent of the Mine-Resistant Ambush-Protective vehicles, or MRAPs, being deployed in Iraq are flown through Turkey. The vehicles are built to withstand roadside bombs.  See Incirlik's key location Â»",
                "pred_ans": "about 70 percent of all air cargo going into iraq",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 46525,
                "question": "what is incirlik air base?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "211:230|523:617|528:617|526:617",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"526:617\": 1, \"523:617\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "southern turkey",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 56297,
                "question": "what does the house resolution call genocide?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "107:154|107:157|None|330:368",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"107:154\": 1, \"330:368\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "turkey ' s treatment of armenians in world war i",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 56573,
                "question": "Does House consider killing of Armenians \"genocide?\"",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|107:129,139:167,87:107",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "some democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious house resolution labeling turkey ' s treatment of armenians in world war i as genocide",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 64626,
                "question": "What did the House resolution call the killing of Armenians?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "157:167|877:910|157:167",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "genocide",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 65479,
                "question": "Who is upset about World War I genocide?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "25:35|129:139|240:248|20:35",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\n\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \"genocide\" label.",
                "pred_ans": "ankara",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 69372,
                "question": "Are Dems \"revisiting their own positions?\"",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|1482:1530,1540:1551",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1482:1530\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Majority Leader Steny Hoyer signaled Tuesday that the vote might be put off.\n\n\"I said I thought we would bring this up prior to us leaving here,\" said Hoyer of Maryland. \"I have not changed on that, although I would be less than candid to say that there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions. We will have to determine where everybody is.\"\n\nDemocratic Rep. Ike Skelton, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, announced his opposition to the resolution last week.",
                "pred_ans": "there are a number of people who are revisiting their own positions",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 72909,
                "question": "What is the key point for U.S. military supply?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1996:2015|2274:2363|None|2044:2067,2071:2114,482:523,526:550,554:617",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"2071:2114\": 1, \"none\": 1, \"482:523\": 1}",
                "para_text": "The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\n\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \"genocide\" label.",
                "pred_ans": "incirlik",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 77395,
                "question": "turkey is upset by what?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "307:351,354:377|116:152,154:167|None|330:351",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"116:152\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "the resolution calling the killing of armenians by ottoman turks genocide",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 80603,
                "question": "Which country is upset about World War 1 \"genocide\" resolution?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "240:248,291:307|107:116|797:804|240:248",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"240:248\": 1, \"107:116\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "turkey",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 83516,
                "question": "What does House resolution call killing of Armenians?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "157:167|157:167",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Some Democrats appear to be wavering on a highly contentious House resolution labeling Turkey's treatment of Armenians in World War I as genocide.\n\nA KC-135 tanker lands at Incirlik Air Base in southern Turkey in 2003.\n\nTurkey, a longtime U.S. ally and NATO partner, was incensed by the resolution calling the killing of Armenians by Ottoman Turks genocide and threatened to block access to Incirlik Air Base after the resolution passed a House committee vote.",
                "pred_ans": "genocide",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 89494,
                "question": "Who were the victims of the \"genocide\"?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "129:139|129:154|833:843|341:351",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"129:139\": 1, \"833:843\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\n\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \"genocide\" label.",
                "pred_ans": "armenians",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 107538,
                "question": "Who is upset about genocide?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "20:35|1250:1262,1615:1628,1756:1771,1786:1798|240:248,291:300,303:318|797:804",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"20:35\": 1, \"797:804\": 1, \"none\": 1}",
                "para_text": "The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\n\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \"genocide\" label.",
                "pred_ans": "ankara",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 109078,
                "question": "What air base is key for US military supply?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "193:202|411:420|193:202",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The Pentagon is preparing to set up new supply routes for troops in Iraq if Turkey cuts off U.S. access to the strategically important Incirlik, military officials said Tuesday.\n\nAnkara acknowledges the killings of Armenians during World War I but vehemently objects to the \"genocide\" label.",
                "pred_ans": "incirlik",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 110781,
                "question": "What are Dems doing?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "107:167,48:107|25:98|None|107:167,35:107",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"35:107\": 1, \"25:98\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Defense Secretary Robert Gates echoed lawmakers' concerns last week.\n\n\"About 70 percent of all air cargo going into Iraq goes through Turkey. ... About a third of the fuel that they consume goes through Turkey or comes from Turkey,\" Gates said.\n\nHe also said that 95 percent of the Mine-Resistant Ambush-Protective vehicles, or MRAPs, being deployed in Iraq are flown through Turkey. The vehicles are built to withstand roadside bombs.  See Incirlik's key location Â»",
                "pred_ans": "mine - resistant ambush - protective vehicles , or mraps , being deployed in iraq are flown through turkey . the vehicles are built to withstand roadside bombs",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 116529,
                "question": "What air base is a key point for U.S. military supply of Iraq mission?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "193:202|193:202",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\" they wrote.\n\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \"a broad range of options\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.",
                "pred_ans": "incirlik air base",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 118494,
                "question": "incirlik air base is the key point of who?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "528:570|2057:2067,2071:2114|554:570|710:715",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"2071:2114\": 1, \"528:570\": 1, \"bad_question\": 1}",
                "para_text": "\"More than half of the cargo flown into Iraq and Afghanistan comes through Incirlik Air Base, and this base would be a key component of any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future,\" they wrote.\n\nLt. Gen. Carter Ham, the director of operations for the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said Pentagon planners are looking at \"a broad range of options\" to keep food, fuel and ammunition flowing to U.S. troops in Iraq if Turkey blocks Incirlik.",
                "pred_ans": "any plans for redeployment of our troops in the future",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "story_id": "./cnn/stories/44fc3a2bc441a674f1ebdeabae73278977909db4.story",
        "story_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.\n\nIslamic extremists in Algeria and other North African countries have struck several times in recent years.\n\nAn al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister's headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\n\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend",
        "questions": [
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 25198,
                "question": "trash3584648386468",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "trash3584648386468 [SEP]",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 27741,
                "question": "Where is the office?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "285:291,302:334|256:334|263:291,302:334|271:279",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"256:334\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "thenia",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 38564,
                "question": "where did the attack occur in Thenia?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "217:256|217:256",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "near an office housing judicial police",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 40675,
                "question": "Where did the attack occur?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "200:209,217:279|30:38|217:334|263:291,302:334",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"217:334\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "thenia",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 43805,
                "question": "Who took responsibility?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "584:606|587:614,822:836|587:614|584:606",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"584:606\": 2}",
                "para_text": "An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister's headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\n\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "al qaeda",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 45436,
                "question": "What was destroyed in the blast?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "167:177,180:188|372:389|372:389",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "about 20 houses",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 47108,
                "question": "What city did the attack occur in?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "180:188|180:188,271:279|180:188",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "thenia",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 48963,
                "question": "Who took responsibility for the attack?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "822:831|822:831",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister's headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\n\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "al qaeda",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 54812,
                "question": "what kind of damage was done",
                "answer_char_ranges": "352:389|362:389,42:62,66:78|362:389|362:389,42:78",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"362:389\": 1, \"352:389\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "the blast destroyed about 20 houses",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 55714,
                "question": "When did the bombing that killed four take place?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "30:38|862:870|209:217|189:217",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"862:870\": 2, \"189:217\": 1}",
                "para_text": "An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister's headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\n\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "january 2",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 64309,
                "question": "The blast did what?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "362:389|42:78|42:55,66:78|362:389",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"42:78\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "destroyed about 20 houses",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 68109,
                "question": "Who took responsibility for the January bombing?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "822:836,860:862,870:872|476:495|822:831,870:872|822:831",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"822:831\": 2}",
                "para_text": "An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister's headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\n\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "al qaeda",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 71564,
                "question": "In what cityy did the attack happen",
                "answer_char_ranges": "180:188|200:209,263:279|271:279|271:279",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"263:279\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "thenia",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 71921,
                "question": "Where did the attacks occur?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "225:279|30:38|271:279,30:38|271:279,314:334",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"225:279\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "thenia",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 74205,
                "question": "trash4564216464",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "trash4564216464 [SEP]",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 75343,
                "question": "Who took responsability for the bombing?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister's headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\n\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "al qaeda",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 81186,
                "question": "the blast destroy how many house?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "352:356,362:389|372:389|378:389|378:389",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"362:389\": 2, \"378:389\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "20",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 83757,
                "question": "Where is the attact occur?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "30:38|30:38",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "thenia",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 84404,
                "question": "what is the count of houses destroyed and people injured?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "378:381,49:55|378:381,66:78|378:381,66:78",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "20",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 89023,
                "question": "WHo said they were responsibble for the blase",
                "answer_char_ranges": "822:831|822:831",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "the algerian press service",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 89298,
                "question": "What did the blast destroy?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "378:389|372:389|378:389",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "about 20 houses",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 91855,
                "question": "where was the bombing of Al Qaeda that killed 4?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "30:38|953:962|953:962",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister's headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\n\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "naciria",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 93653,
                "question": "354d6+84684gf6ser4g864sr6g8rg",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "[SEP]",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 94102,
                "question": "Who took responsibility for the bombing?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "587:606|587:606",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister's headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\n\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "al qaeda",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 95678,
                "question": "what time I happened Thenia attack?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "200:217|209:217|None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"209:217\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "tuesday",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 106165,
                "question": "What was the amount of victims of the attack?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "42:78|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"42:78\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "three",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 113882,
                "question": "Who took responsibility for the bombing that killed four?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "587:606|822:836,860:872|584:606|822:831",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"822:831\": 2}",
                "para_text": "An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister's headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\n\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "al qaeda",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 116745,
                "question": "which group took responsibility for the bombing?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "822:831|822:831",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "An al Qaeda affiliate claimed responsibility last year for the deadliest attack in Algiers in 10 years, a bombing that destroyed the prime minister's headquarters and a police base, killing at least 24 people and wounding more than 220.\n\nAl Qaeda also took responsibility for a January 2 bombing that killed four and wounded 20 at a building housing security forces in Naciria, a city about 50 km (31 miles) east of Algiers. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "al qaeda",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 119021,
                "question": "there was some died in the explosion?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "42:62|42:62",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- A car bomb attack in Algeria has killed three people and wounded 23, the Algerian Press Service reported.\n\nAn Algerian policeman stands in front of destroyed buildings in Thenia.\n\nThe attack occurred Tuesday near an office housing judicial police in the city of Thenia, about 50 km (31 miles) east of the capital of Algiers, the agency said.\n\nThe blast destroyed about 20 houses, and a commission has been appointed to look after the victims, the press agency said.",
                "pred_ans": "three",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "story_id": "./cnn/stories/d49c8ddc7586fcc27a7d310a5cb7703f19e4607d.story",
        "story_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.\n\nTreviso fire officials said one of the dead was a woman, and said no one on the ground was hurt.\n\nThe U.S. military said the helicopter was an Army H-60 Black Hawk attached to the 1st Battalion, 214th Aviation Regiment.\n\nThe military was not releasing the names of those killed, pending notification of the victims' families.\n\nPolice and fire officials said the craft crashed in an open area near the Piave River north of Treviso, between the towns of Maserata Sul Piave and Santa Lucia Di Piave.  Watch scenes of the crash site in northern Italy Â»\n\nThe helicopter appeared crumpled and charred in photos from the crash.\n\nItaly's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.\n\nThe military has employed Black Hawks for about three decades. The helicopter's first combat mission was about 25 years ago.  E-mail to a friend\n\nCNN's Hada Messia and Barbara Starr contributed to this report.",
        "questions": [
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 4885,
                "question": "What number  of people  died  in crash",
                "answer_char_ranges": "307:312|307:312,319:331,368:397|307:312",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 6229,
                "question": "Where did the helicopter leave from?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "292:307|1224:1241|1224:1241",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Italy's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.",
                "pred_ans": "aviano air base",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 11418,
                "question": "What killed 4 and injured 2?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "103:122,92:103|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"103:122\": 2}",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "black hawk helicopter crashed",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 20042,
                "question": "What is the number of confirmed deaths in helicopter crash?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "23:54|307:319|23:29|307:319,372:403",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"307:319\": 1, \"23:29\": 1, \"23:54\": 1}",
                "para_text": "Italy's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.",
                "pred_ans": "what",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 26891,
                "question": "what happen so four people died?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "103:122,92:103|103:144,92:103|103:122,92:103",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "the crash",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 35125,
                "question": "What number of people died in the crash?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "23:29|23:29",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "four",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 37624,
                "question": "What killed 4 people?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "196:208,361:368|103:144,92:103|103:122,92:103|103:122,90:103",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"103:144\": 1, \"92:103\": 2}",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "black hawk helicopter crashed",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 42300,
                "question": "What killed four people?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "103:122,319:324,354:368,90:103|103:122,92:103|103:114,1080:1103,114:122,361:368,786:804,92:103|103:122,92:103",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1080:1103\": 1, \"90:103\": 2}",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "black hawk helicopter crashed",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 46909,
                "question": "What amount of people were aboard the black hawk helicopter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "217:245|217:245",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "11 u . s . military personnel",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 49716,
                "question": "Where did the response copter take off from?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1224:1241|1194:1215,1224:1241|1224:1241",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Italy's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.",
                "pred_ans": "aviano air base",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 52895,
                "question": "black hawn helicpter aboard how many people?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "217:220|217:220",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "11",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 62481,
                "question": "Where is aviano base?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "300:307|125:144|859:867,871:877,880:899,903:925,960:975|300:307",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"125:144\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Italy's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.",
                "pred_ans": "italy",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 67655,
                "question": "what was the name of the helicopter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "92:103|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"92:103\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The U.S. military said the helicopter was an Army H-60 Black Hawk attached to the 1st Battalion, 214th Aviation Regiment.\n\nThe military was not releasing the names of those killed, pending notification of the victims' families.\n\nPolice and fire officials said the craft crashed in an open area near the Piave River north of Treviso, between the towns of Maserata Sul Piave and Santa Lucia Di Piave.  Watch scenes of the crash site in northern Italy Â»",
                "pred_ans": "an army h - 60 black hawk",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 68470,
                "question": "Who is responsible for this crash?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "157:175|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 1, \"157:175\": 2}",
                "para_text": "CNN's Hada Messia and Barbara Starr contributed to this report.",
                "pred_ans": "hada messia and barbara starr",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 70329,
                "question": "What was the number of people on the helicopter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "217:220|217:245|217:220",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The U.S. military said the helicopter was an Army H-60 Black Hawk attached to the 1st Battalion, 214th Aviation Regiment.\n\nThe military was not releasing the names of those killed, pending notification of the victims' families.\n\nPolice and fire officials said the craft crashed in an open area near the Piave River north of Treviso, between the towns of Maserata Sul Piave and Santa Lucia Di Piave.  Watch scenes of the crash site in northern Italy Â»",
                "pred_ans": "1st battalion , 214th aviation regiment . the military was not releasing the names of those killed",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 71771,
                "question": "What number of people were aboard the helicopter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "217:245|217:245",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "11",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 72675,
                "question": "What was make of Helicopter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "92:103|571:592|568:592,92:103|571:592",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"568:592\": 1, \"571:592\": 1, \"92:103\": 1}",
                "para_text": "The U.S. military said the helicopter was an Army H-60 Black Hawk attached to the 1st Battalion, 214th Aviation Regiment.\n\nThe military was not releasing the names of those killed, pending notification of the victims' families.\n\nPolice and fire officials said the craft crashed in an open area near the Piave River north of Treviso, between the towns of Maserata Sul Piave and Santa Lucia Di Piave.  Watch scenes of the crash site in northern Italy Â»",
                "pred_ans": "h - 60 black hawk",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 74044,
                "question": "What number of people were aboard?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "217:220|217:245|217:220",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "11 u . s . military personnel",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 76120,
                "question": "What caused the crash?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|103:114",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The U.S. military said the helicopter was an Army H-60 Black Hawk attached to the 1st Battalion, 214th Aviation Regiment.\n\nThe military was not releasing the names of those killed, pending notification of the victims' families.\n\nPolice and fire officials said the craft crashed in an open area near the Piave River north of Treviso, between the towns of Maserata Sul Piave and Santa Lucia Di Piave.  Watch scenes of the crash site in northern Italy Â»",
                "pred_ans": "helicopter",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 81389,
                "question": "Who died in the helicopter crash?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "208:220,21:23,220:234,23:49,54:61|307:331|None|21:49",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"220:234\": 1, \"307:331\": 1, \"21:49\": 1}",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "a sixth u . s . service member",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 88173,
                "question": "what did copter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "114:144|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"114:144\": 1, \"bad_question\": 2}",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "carrying 11 u . s . military personnel",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 90756,
                "question": "Who was on the helicopter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "217:245|23:49|217:245",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Italy's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.",
                "pred_ans": "italy ' s ansa news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution . ansa said the helicopter had taken off from aviano air base",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 92783,
                "question": "Where did the copter take off from?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1180:1215,1224:1241|1224:1241|1224:1241",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Italy's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.",
                "pred_ans": "aviano air base",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 92890,
                "question": "Where did copter take off from?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|1224:1241",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1224:1241\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Italy's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.",
                "pred_ans": "aviano air base",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 92947,
                "question": "What number of people were on the helicopter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "217:220|217:220",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "ROME, Italy (CNN) -- A sixth U.S. service member died Friday from injuries sustained when a Black Hawk helicopter crashed in northeastern Italy on Thursday, the U.S. military in Europe said.\n\nThe helicopter, carrying 11 U.S. military personnel, crashed Thursday afternoon about 22 miles from Aviano, Italy. Four people were killed and seven were injured in the crash, and two of the injured later died, the U.S. military said.",
                "pred_ans": "11",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 97483,
                "question": "who was killed?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "307:319|220:245|220:245,307:324,372:403|307:324,653:662,666:699",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"307:319\": 2, \"220:245\": 1}",
                "para_text": "The U.S. military said the helicopter was an Army H-60 Black Hawk attached to the 1st Battalion, 214th Aviation Regiment.\n\nThe military was not releasing the names of those killed, pending notification of the victims' families.\n\nPolice and fire officials said the craft crashed in an open area near the Piave River north of Treviso, between the towns of Maserata Sul Piave and Santa Lucia Di Piave.  Watch scenes of the crash site in northern Italy Â»",
                "pred_ans": "the military was not releasing the names of those killed , pending notification of the victims ' families",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 102630,
                "question": "where did it take off from?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1224:1241|1190:1215,1224:1241|138:144|1224:1241",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1224:1241\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Italy's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.",
                "pred_ans": "aviano air base",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 108251,
                "question": "Was it mechanical failure?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Italy's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.",
                "pred_ans": "the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution . ansa said the helicopter had taken off from aviano air base , but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 119581,
                "question": "Where was the helicopter taking off from?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1224:1241|1224:1241",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Italy's ANSA news agency said the helicopter crashed near the bridge of a major highway and the road was closed as a precaution.\n\nANSA said the helicopter had taken off from Aviano Air Base, but fire authorities could not confirm whether it was leaving or returning to the base.\n\nThe Black Hawk is considered the workhorse of the military's helicopter fleet. It is used in missions in Iraq and Afghanistan to carry troops and equipment.",
                "pred_ans": "aviano air base",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "story_id": "./cnn/stories/d256aee1a47eb5b489dee6fb72ab7f7d1483a37f.story",
        "story_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.\n\nPratibha Patil, the ruling coalition's 72-year-old nominee for the mainly ceremonial post, easily beat opposition-backed challenger and vice president, Bhairon Singh Shekhawat, in a vote by the national parliament and state politicians.\n\n\"This a victory of the people,\" Patil told reporters after official results were announced Saturday. \"I am grateful to the people of India and the men and women of India and this is a victory for the principles which our Indian people uphold.\"\n\nPatil won about two thirds of the electoral college votes. There had never been any doubt she would win, given support from the ruling coalition.\n\nThe governor of the northwestern desert state of Rajasthan, she emerged on the national stage when the Congress-led coalition and its communist allies failed to agree on a joint candidate.\n\n\"This is a very special moment for us women, and men of course, in our country because for the first time we have a woman being elected president of India,\" Congress party leader Sonia Gandhi, India's most powerful politician, said.\n\nSupporters hoped Patil's candidacy would help bring issues that plague women in India, like dowry-related violence, into the public spotlight. A woman is murdered, raped or abused every three minutes on average in India.\n\nHer presidency also reflects the growing power of some women in India, where an increasing number are taking part in the workforce and in schools and hold senior positions in corporations.\n\nAfter the results, Patil supporters took to the streets, singing and dancing as others lit fire crackers and beat large brass drums.\n\nIndia has had a number of female icons in the past -- most famously Sonia Gandhi's mother-in-law, Indira, who was one of the world's first female prime ministers in 1966.\n\nBut hope Patil's presidency would spark only positive talk about women's influence in India evaporated when it emerged the bank for women she helped established was closed in 2003 because of bad debts and amid accusations of financial irregularities.\n\nThe employees' union has taken Patil and others to court, claiming loans meant for poor women were instead given to her brother and other relatives and not returned. She was also accused of trying to shield her brother in a murder inquiry.\n\nPrime Minister Manmohan Singh, who has dismissed accusations against her as \"mud-slinging\", said on Saturday her victory was \"a vote against the politics of divisiveness\".\n\n\"All the allegations against me are motivated and have already been answered,\" Patil said in a statement last week.\n\nHer campaign was marked by other mishaps as well.\n\nShe managed to offend many minority Muslims, and anger some historians, by saying Indian women first veiled their heads as protection against 16th century Muslim invaders.\n\nThen she dismayed modern India by claiming she had experienced a \"divine premonition\" that she was destined for higher office from a long dead spiritual guru.\n\nCritics also dug up a comment she was said to have made as Maharashtra's health minister in 1975, saying people with hereditary diseases should be sterilized. E-mail to a friend",
        "questions": [
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 1975,
                "question": "what was the election campaign marked by?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "223:232|223:232",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Her campaign was marked by other mishaps as well.\n\nShe managed to offend many minority Muslims, and anger some historians, by saying Indian women first veiled their heads as protection against 16th century Muslim invaders.\n\nThen she dismayed modern India by claiming she had experienced a \"divine premonition\" that she was destined for higher office from a long dead spiritual guru.",
                "pred_ans": "mishaps",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 2153,
                "question": "What are the reasons that Pratibha Patil's supporters are calling her victory a boost for women's rights?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1397:1410,1415:1467|1386:1410,1415:1494|256:296|30:76",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1415:1494\": 1, \"256:296\": 1, \"30:76\": 1}",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "millions of downtrodden women , despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 3544,
                "question": "What are the reasons that the bitter election campaign was marked by scandal?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "2188:2230,2234:2320,2321:2491,2495:2561|2388:2394,2400:2420,2428:2449|2260:2320,2487:2561|2188:2230,2234:2320,2388:2487,2511:2561,2918:2948,2952:2975,3085:3107,3334:3395",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 1, \"2511:2561\": 1, \"2260:2320\": 1}",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 12310,
                "question": "what is a bppst for women's rights?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|48:76",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2}",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "",
                "exact_match": 2,
                "class": 2
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 16239,
                "question": "Who was the coalition's nominee?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "297:313|297:313",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "After the results, Patil supporters took to the streets, singing and dancing as others lit fire crackers and beat large brass drums.\n\nIndia has had a number of female icons in the past -- most famously Sonia Gandhi's mother-in-law, Indira, who was one of the world's first female prime ministers in 1966.",
                "pred_ans": "patil",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 20588,
                "question": "What kind of election campaign was it?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "197:204|195:204|2638:2654|197:204",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"197:204\": 2, \"2638:2654\": 1}",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "bitter",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 21883,
                "question": "Which country elected it's first female president?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1266:1274,256:264|30:36|30:36",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "india",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 23848,
                "question": "Who was the first female president of India?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "233:249|233:249",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "pratibha patil",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 44508,
                "question": "What is Patil's age?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "249:253|249:253",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "72",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 45970,
                "question": "What is the age of President Elect Patil?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "249:253|336:348|249:253",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "72",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 51784,
                "question": "what was the scandal?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "195:213|2192:2230,2234:2249,2388:2449,2985:3011,3017:3023,3026:3075|2192:2230,2234:2320|30:76",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"30:76\": 1, \"2388:2449\": 2}",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "a bitter campaign",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 54703,
                "question": "What number of female presidents have been elected?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "264:270|52:58|48:58|264:270",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"48:58\": 1, \"none\": 1, \"52:58\": 1}",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "72",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 67143,
                "question": "Was the election campaign marked by scandal?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "195:232|195:204",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"195:232\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Her campaign was marked by other mishaps as well.\n\nShe managed to offend many minority Muslims, and anger some historians, by saying Indian women first veiled their heads as protection against 16th century Muslim invaders.\n\nThen she dismayed modern India by claiming she had experienced a \"divine premonition\" that she was destined for higher office from a long dead spiritual guru.",
                "pred_ans": "her campaign was marked by other mishaps",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 69990,
                "question": "Who was was the ruling coalition's nominee?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "297:317|297:313|297:313",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"This a victory of the people,\" Patil told reporters after official results were announced Saturday. \"I am grateful to the people of India and the men and women of India and this is a victory for the principles which our Indian people uphold.\"\n\nPatil won about two thirds of the electoral college votes. There had never been any doubt she would win, given support from the ruling coalition.",
                "pred_ans": "patil",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 69991,
                "question": "Who's supporters are calling the victory a boost for women's rights?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "233:249,30:36|297:313|233:249|233:249",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"233:249\": 2}",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "",
                "exact_match": 2,
                "class": 2
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 78262,
                "question": "What age was Patil at the time of the election?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "336:348|249:253|249:253",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"This a victory of the people,\" Patil told reporters after official results were announced Saturday. \"I am grateful to the people of India and the men and women of India and this is a victory for the principles which our Indian people uphold.\"\n\nPatil won about two thirds of the electoral college votes. There had never been any doubt she would win, given support from the ruling coalition.",
                "pred_ans": "saturday",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 86053,
                "question": "What was marked by scandal?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "204:213|195:213|195:213",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "a bitter campaign",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 86526,
                "question": "What happened during the election?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "40:76|52:76|233:296|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"233:296\": 1, \"52:76\": 1, \"40:76\": 1}",
                "para_text": "\"This a victory of the people,\" Patil told reporters after official results were announced Saturday. \"I am grateful to the people of India and the men and women of India and this is a victory for the principles which our Indian people uphold.\"\n\nPatil won about two thirds of the electoral college votes. There had never been any doubt she would win, given support from the ruling coalition.",
                "pred_ans": "official results were announced saturday",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 88076,
                "question": "What nation elected their first female president?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "256:264|30:36|30:36",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "india",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 92620,
                "question": "What is the victory being called?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "551:567|551:567",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"This a victory of the people,\" Patil told reporters after official results were announced Saturday. \"I am grateful to the people of India and the men and women of India and this is a victory for the principles which our Indian people uphold.\"\n\nPatil won about two thirds of the electoral college votes. There had never been any doubt she would win, given support from the ruling coalition.",
                "pred_ans": "victory of the people",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 98044,
                "question": "Who is the president of India?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "233:249|233:249",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "pratibha patil",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 99419,
                "question": "What is the name of the president elect?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "233:249|233:249",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "pratibha patil",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 100758,
                "question": "is a female president a good idea?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1128:1148,1212:1253,1263:1274,1351:1438|132:153,156:165,168:187|None|2852:2902,3258:3266,3287:3292,3295:3325",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2, \"132:153\": 1}",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 101140,
                "question": "Who did India elect as the first female president on Saturday?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "233:264,270:278|233:249|233:249",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "pratibha patil",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 101797,
                "question": "What is Patil's first name?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "233:242|233:242",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "pratibha",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 103296,
                "question": "who cares about womens rights?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "30:36|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"30:36\": 2}",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "",
                "exact_match": 2,
                "class": 2
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 104909,
                "question": "What age is the new president?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "249:253|233:253|249:253",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "72",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 109068,
                "question": "who is india's first female president?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "233:249|233:249",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "pratibha patil",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 117011,
                "question": "Whom did India elect president?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "233:249|233:249",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "NEW DELHI, India (Reuters) -- India has elected its first female president, official results show, in what supporters are calling a boost for the rights of millions of downtrodden women, despite a bitter campaign marked by scandal.\n\nPratibha Patil, 72, is India's first elected female president.",
                "pred_ans": "pratibha patil",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 117748,
                "question": "What is her name?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "233:249|233:249",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The employees' union has taken Patil and others to court, claiming loans meant for poor women were instead given to her brother and other relatives and not returned. She was also accused of trying to shield her brother in a murder inquiry.\n\nPrime Minister Manmohan Singh, who has dismissed accusations against her as \"mud-slinging\", said on Saturday her victory was \"a vote against the politics of divisiveness\".",
                "pred_ans": "patil",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "story_id": "./cnn/stories/30cb674030b01014d2c87b92f09152857e249631.story",
        "story_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.\n\nA statement from Nigerian Breweries on Monday said Ogadje died suddenly and he was thought to have drowned.\n\n\"All attempts to revive him by the attendant medical team and the lifeguards, including his fellow contestants, failed,\" said Nigerian Breweries, which is majority-owned by the Dutch giant. Broadcasting had been due to start on Thursday.\n\nIn the show, the weakest contestants are evicted one by one until a winner emerges. The prize money is a big attraction in a country where most people live in extreme poverty and benefit little from Nigeria's oil wealth.\n\nThe winner was to get 5 million naira (about $39,000) in cash, a four-wheel drive jeep and another 500,000 naira (about $3,900) to buy clothes. The winner could also have expected to become an instant celebrity, attracting sponsorship deals.\n\nThe Ultimate Search, which started in 2004, gets high ratings. E-mail to a friend",
        "questions": [
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 19041,
                "question": "Which company sponsors the show Gulder Ultimate Search?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "159:170|146:170|146:181,187:205|159:170",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"159:170\": 2, \"146:170\": 1}",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "heineken",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 25689,
                "question": "where did anthony drowned?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "271:288|271:321|271:321",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "shere hills lake",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 26795,
                "question": "What program does Heineken sponsor?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "340:366|28:63|340:366",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "nigeria ' s television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program , said dutch brewer heineken ' s local unit which is sponsoring the show . anthony ogadje , 25 , and nine other contestants had gone to shere hills lake in nigeria ' s hilly plateau state to prepare for the \" gulder ultimate search",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 28014,
                "question": "WHAT COMPANY SPONSORS THE PROGRAM?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "159:170|146:170|146:181|146:181",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"146:170\": 2, \"146:181\": 1}",
                "para_text": "\"All attempts to revive him by the attendant medical team and the lifeguards, including his fellow contestants, failed,\" said Nigerian Breweries, which is majority-owned by the Dutch giant. Broadcasting had been due to start on Thursday.\n\nIn the show, the weakest contestants are evicted one by one until a winner emerges. The prize money is a big attraction in a country where most people live in extreme poverty and benefit little from Nigeria's oil wealth.",
                "pred_ans": "nigerian breweries",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 29508,
                "question": "What age was Anthony Ogadje when he died?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "228:232|228:232",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "25",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 33559,
                "question": "Where did Anthony Ogadje die?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "271:321|271:288|271:301|271:321",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"271:288\": 1, \"271:321\": 1, \"271:301\": 1}",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "shere hills lake",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 38521,
                "question": "Who were the sponsors of his show?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "159:170|146:181,446:465|159:170",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"All attempts to revive him by the attendant medical team and the lifeguards, including his fellow contestants, failed,\" said Nigerian Breweries, which is majority-owned by the Dutch giant. Broadcasting had been due to start on Thursday.\n\nIn the show, the weakest contestants are evicted one by one until a winner emerges. The prize money is a big attraction in a country where most people live in extreme poverty and benefit little from Nigeria's oil wealth.",
                "pred_ans": "nigerian breweries",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 39624,
                "question": "What was Anthony Odagje doing at the time of his death?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "528:537|259:366|112:141|528:537",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"259:366\": 2}",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "gone to shere hills lake",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 42255,
                "question": "Where did Anthony Ogadje drown",
                "answer_char_ranges": "271:288|271:288",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "shere hills lake",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 45257,
                "question": "WHAT WAS HE PREPARING FOR?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "340:366|112:124,128:141|49:63|128:141,340:366",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"128:141\": 1, \"340:366\": 2}",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "gulder ultimate search , \"",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 46980,
                "question": "Who sponsors the program",
                "answer_char_ranges": "159:170|146:181|146:181",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"All attempts to revive him by the attendant medical team and the lifeguards, including his fellow contestants, failed,\" said Nigerian Breweries, which is majority-owned by the Dutch giant. Broadcasting had been due to start on Thursday.\n\nIn the show, the weakest contestants are evicted one by one until a winner emerges. The prize money is a big attraction in a country where most people live in extreme poverty and benefit little from Nigeria's oil wealth.",
                "pred_ans": "nigerian breweries",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 51650,
                "question": "Who drowned in Shere HIlls Lake?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "480:487|212:228|212:228",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "anthony ogadje",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 56839,
                "question": "What age was Anthony Ogadje?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "228:232|228:232",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "25",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 59920,
                "question": "who was the sponsor?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "446:465|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 1, \"446:465\": 2}",
                "para_text": "\"All attempts to revive him by the attendant medical team and the lifeguards, including his fellow contestants, failed,\" said Nigerian Breweries, which is majority-owned by the Dutch giant. Broadcasting had been due to start on Thursday.\n\nIn the show, the weakest contestants are evicted one by one until a winner emerges. The prize money is a big attraction in a country where most people live in extreme poverty and benefit little from Nigeria's oil wealth.",
                "pred_ans": "nigerian breweries",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 71810,
                "question": "Which country is Heineken from?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "146:152|146:152",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"All attempts to revive him by the attendant medical team and the lifeguards, including his fellow contestants, failed,\" said Nigerian Breweries, which is majority-owned by the Dutch giant. Broadcasting had been due to start on Thursday.\n\nIn the show, the weakest contestants are evicted one by one until a winner emerges. The prize money is a big attraction in a country where most people live in extreme poverty and benefit little from Nigeria's oil wealth.",
                "pred_ans": "dutch",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 90784,
                "question": "What was he doing?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "324:366|101:141|321:366|112:124,132:141",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"101:141\": 2}",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "gone to shere hills lake in nigeria ' s hilly plateau state to prepare for the \" gulder ultimate search , \"",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 91379,
                "question": "WHERE DID ANTHONY OGADJE REPORTEDLY DROWN?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "271:321|271:321",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "shere hills lake",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 92986,
                "question": "What was his age?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "228:232|228:232",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"All attempts to revive him by the attendant medical team and the lifeguards, including his fellow contestants, failed,\" said Nigerian Breweries, which is majority-owned by the Dutch giant. Broadcasting had been due to start on Thursday.\n\nIn the show, the weakest contestants are evicted one by one until a winner emerges. The prize money is a big attraction in a country where most people live in extreme poverty and benefit little from Nigeria's oil wealth.",
                "pred_ans": "what",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 95387,
                "question": "what is heineken?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "146:159|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"146:159\": 2, \"none\": 1}",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "dutch brewer",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 97457,
                "question": "What age was Mr Ogadje",
                "answer_char_ranges": "212:220,228:232|228:232|228:232",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "25",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 98792,
                "question": "What happened?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "101:141,28:101|101:141,28:101",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "a contestant drowned",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 101706,
                "question": "Who sponsors the show \"Gulder Ultimate Search\"?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "146:181|146:170|159:170|146:170",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"159:170\": 2}",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "heineken",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 103583,
                "question": "Which Dutch brewer sponsored the program",
                "answer_char_ranges": "159:181|159:181,187:211|159:170|159:170",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"159:181\": 2}",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "heineken",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 104910,
                "question": "who is anthony?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "247:259,332:336,340:366|220:232|247:259|247:259",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2, \"220:232\": 1}",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "",
                "exact_match": 2,
                "class": 2
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 115236,
                "question": "What show was he preparing for?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "340:366|340:366",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "LAGOS, Nigeria (Reuters) -- Nigeria's television survival show has been suspended after a contestant drowned in preparation for the program, said Dutch brewer Heineken's local unit which is sponsoring the show.\n\nAnthony Ogadje, 25, and nine other contestants had gone to Shere Hills Lake in Nigeria's hilly Plateau State to prepare for the \"Gulder Ultimate Search,\" which sets a variety of physical challenges for participants.",
                "pred_ans": "gulder ultimate search",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "story_id": "./cnn/stories/d5342fb6d8d522f336f2ce34eaa6e62446c0da2e.story",
        "story_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.\n\nDressed in a tailored, black pantsuit, Lafave said she had \"innocent\" physical contact with a female co-worker she knew as under age 18.  Watch Lafave in the courtroom Â»\n\nAt the time, she and the 17-year-old hostess worked at Danny Boy's, a small restaurant in the Tampa, Florida, area.\n\nLafave, 27, pleaded guilty in November 2005 to having sex with a 14-year-old boy and was sentenced to three years under house arrest and seven years of probation.\n\nLafave was required to register as a sex offender and ordered not to have any contact with minors. A tracking device she carries as part of her probation went off in court, prompting the prosecutor to observe, \"I think she's accounted for.\"\n\nLafave acknowledged she was aware that hugs and other forms of physical contact -- as well as conversations about sex -- with minors violated terms of her probation. She referred to the sexually explicit conversations at work as just \"girl talk.\"\n\nLafave denied talking about her sex life with co-workers. \"I don't speak that way about my personal life,\" she said. But she added that her co-workers spoke freely about sex in a \"small group setting.\"\n\nWhile other co-workers socialized outside work, Lafave said, the 17-year-old was not included in those outings.\n\nAsked why she hugged the young co-worker, Lafave explained it was a small restaurant with a casual atmosphere where co-workers felt like family. The contact came, she said, \"out of my good nature, that's the way it worked.\"\n\nThe contacts that led to Thursday's probation violation hearing first surfaced during two polygraph tests administered as part of Lafave's court-ordered supervision.\n\nShe received a verbal reprimand a year ago, according to testimony. When the behavior continued, her probation officer asked a judge to find her in violation.\n\nShe was ordered to quit the restaurant job and now works as a receptionist in her mother's beauty shop.\n\nIn the past, Lafave has said she suffers from bipolar disorder and is receiving treatment. E-mail to a friend",
        "questions": [
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 698,
                "question": "What warning did the judge give Debra Lafave?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|2094:2138,2162:2221,2227:2253,405:443",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2, \"405:443\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "",
                "exact_match": 2,
                "class": 2
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 2375,
                "question": "What does lafave's Probation forbid her from?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "247:304|274:304|965:995|1192:1218,1259:1271",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"965:995\": 1, \"274:304\": 2}",
                "para_text": "She was ordered to quit the restaurant job and now works as a receptionist in her mother's beauty shop.\n\nIn the past, Lafave has said she suffers from bipolar disorder and is receiving treatment. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "quit the restaurant job",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 2924,
                "question": "What did the judge say to Lafave?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "373:404,405:431|405:431|405:431",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "the violation was \" not willful and substantial . \"",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 10654,
                "question": "What did judge find?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "104:157,15:23,27:64,9:15|348:404|104:127,15:23,9:15|104:157",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"104:127\": 1, \"none\": 1, \"104:157\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "debra lafave , the former florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student , violated her probation by hugging a young co - worker , a florida judge found thursday",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 13312,
                "question": "Did the judge find the teacher in violation of her probation?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "104:113|104:113,157:167,173:179|104:113,15:23,1952:1963,1983:2093,2162:2171,2205:2221,2227:2230,305:313,323:359,369:404,9:15|323:359,369:404",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2, \"173:179\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "violated her probation by hugging a young co - worker , a florida judge found thursday",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 17365,
                "question": "What minimum age is Lafave prohibited from having contact with?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|247:251,254:274,287:304",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"287:304\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "18",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 20770,
                "question": "What is Debra Lafave's occupation?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "42:64|42:64",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "florida middle school teacher",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 27209,
                "question": "what is the teacher accused of?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "222:247|74:104|None|77:104",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"74:104\": 2, \"77:104\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "having sex with a student",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 31558,
                "question": "what else did the judge say?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "405:431|405:431",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "the violation was \" not willful and substantial . \"",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 32845,
                "question": "Who is she not allowed to be in contact with?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "287:304|1264:1271|965:974,987:995|287:304",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1264:1271\": 2, \"287:304\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "anyone under 18",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 37809,
                "question": "What are the terms of Lafave's probation?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "907:995|254:304|247:304|1177:1182,1186:1218,1232:1256,1259:1271",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"247:304\": 1, \"907:995\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Asked why she hugged the young co-worker, Lafave explained it was a small restaurant with a casual atmosphere where co-workers felt like family. The contact came, she said, \"out of my good nature, that's the way it worked.\"\n\nThe contacts that led to Thursday's probation violation hearing first surfaced during two polygraph tests administered as part of Lafave's court-ordered supervision.",
                "pred_ans": "two polygraph tests administered as part of lafave ' s court - ordered supervision",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 42203,
                "question": "What is the name of the teacher in the case?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "15:23,9:15|15:23,9:15",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "She was ordered to quit the restaurant job and now works as a receptionist in her mother's beauty shop.\n\nIn the past, Lafave has said she suffers from bipolar disorder and is receiving treatment. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "lafave",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 42417,
                "question": "Will Debra Lafave go to jail",
                "answer_char_ranges": "319:332|309:332|319:332",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "the judge did not send lafave to jail",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 45003,
                "question": "What was the former teacher's name?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "15:23,9:15|15:23,9:15",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "debra lafave",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 58785,
                "question": "What was Lafave's former job?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|42:64",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"42:64\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "florida middle school teacher",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 59997,
                "question": "Who was spared from jail?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "15:23,9:15|332:339|15:23,9:15",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "She was ordered to quit the restaurant job and now works as a receptionist in her mother's beauty shop.\n\nIn the past, Lafave has said she suffers from bipolar disorder and is receiving treatment. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "lafave",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 63307,
                "question": "what judge warns Debra?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "405:431|405:431",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "a florida",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 69091,
                "question": "What did the judge find former teacher",
                "answer_char_ranges": "323:348|104:157|104:127|104:127",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"104:157\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "debra lafave",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 73701,
                "question": "What were the charges against the former teacher?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "834:895|104:157|104:157",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "having sex with a student",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 77278,
                "question": "What are the terms of her probation",
                "answer_char_ranges": "919:995|1177:1218,1221:1256,1259:1280,1286:1289,919:946,950:995|254:304|907:995",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"907:995\": 1, \"919:995\": 1, \"254:304\": 1}",
                "para_text": "Lafave acknowledged she was aware that hugs and other forms of physical contact -- as well as conversations about sex -- with minors violated terms of her probation. She referred to the sexually explicit conversations at work as just \"girl talk.\"\n\nLafave denied talking about her sex life with co-workers. \"I don't speak that way about my personal life,\" she said. But she added that her co-workers spoke freely about sex in a \"small group setting.\"",
                "pred_ans": "lafave acknowledged she was aware that hugs and other forms of physical contact - - as well as conversations about sex - - with minors violated terms of her probation",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 79175,
                "question": "what did she do?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "104:157|104:157,15:23,9:15|499:545|77:104",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"104:157\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "violated her probation by hugging a young co - worker",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 79737,
                "question": "What does a judge warn Debra lafave?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|413:431",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"413:431\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "",
                "exact_match": 2,
                "class": 2
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 85427,
                "question": "what was violated?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "117:127|113:127|113:138,140:157|113:127",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2, \"117:127\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "probation",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 100031,
                "question": "What does Debra Lafave's probation forbid her from doing?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "266:304|266:304",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "have contact with anyone under 18",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 104054,
                "question": "Does the judge find?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "373:404|104:127|None|348:355,373:404",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "the judge did not send lafave to jail",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 104800,
                "question": "What does Lafave probation forbid?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "269:304|903:907,950:970,974:995|130:157|247:304",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"269:304\": 2, \"247:304\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "she is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 109294,
                "question": "What does the probation forbid her from?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "130:157|274:304|1177:1182,1192:1198,1201:1218,1232:1256,1259:1271,130:138,140:157,254:266,274:282,287:304,958:962,965:995|896:907,950:970,974:995",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"965:995\": 1, \"274:304\": 2}",
                "para_text": "She was ordered to quit the restaurant job and now works as a receptionist in her mother's beauty shop.\n\nIn the past, Lafave has said she suffers from bipolar disorder and is receiving treatment. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "quit the restaurant job",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 110510,
                "question": "Who was found to be in violation of probation?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "15:23,9:15|104:117,15:23,9:15|15:23,9:15",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "debra lafave",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 116188,
                "question": "what forbids Lafave's probation to Debra?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "958:962,965:970,974:995|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"974:995\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "she is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 116262,
                "question": "What did the judge find the former teacher for?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "77:104|104:157|None|104:157",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"bad_question\": 1, \"104:157\": 1, \"77:104\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Debra Lafave, the former Florida middle school teacher convicted of having sex with a student, violated her probation by hugging a young co-worker, a Florida judge found Thursday.\n\nDebra Lafave was arrested after talking with a teenager. She is not allowed to have contact with anyone under 18.\n\nBut the judge did not send Lafave to jail, saying the violation was \"not willful and substantial.\"\n\n\"Please don't come back,\" he scolded.",
                "pred_ans": "having sex with a student",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "story_id": "./cnn/stories/35f0e33de7923036a97ac245d899f990bda5e242.story",
        "story_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.\n\nThe president's doctor had recommended a repeat procedure in about five years.\n\nThe procedure will be supervised by Dr. Richard Tubb and conducted by a multidisciplinary team from the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nA colonoscopy is the most sensitive test for colon cancer, rectal cancer and polyps, small clumps of cells that can become cancerous, according to the Mayo Clinic. Small polyps may be removed during the procedure.\n\nSnow said that was the case when Bush had colonoscopies before becoming president.\n\nSnow himself is undergoing chemotherapy for cancer that began in his colon and spread to his liver.\n\nSnow told reporters he had a chemo session scheduled later Friday.  Watch Snow talk about Bush's procedure and his own colon cancer Â»\n\n\"The president wants to encourage everybody to use surveillance,\" Snow said.\n\nThe American Cancer Society recommends that people without high-risk factors or symptoms begin getting screened for signs of colorectal cancer at age 50. E-mail to a friend",
        "questions": [
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 611,
                "question": "When did he last have a colonoscopy?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "386:397|386:397",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "june 2002",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 1829,
                "question": "Where will his powers be transferred?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "20:47|25:35,321:333|None|20:47",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"321:333\": 1, \"20:47\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The procedure will be supervised by Dr. Richard Tubb and conducted by a multidisciplinary team from the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nA colonoscopy is the most sensitive test for colon cancer, rectal cancer and polyps, small clumps of cells that can become cancerous, according to the Mayo Clinic. Small polyps may be removed during the procedure.\n\nSnow said that was the case when Bush had colonoscopies before becoming president.",
                "pred_ans": "national naval medical center in bethesda , maryland",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 3956,
                "question": "what procedure will president bush have?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "138:159|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"138:159\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "colonoscopy",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 14460,
                "question": "What kind of exam is Bush having?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "146:159|367:379|146:159",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "",
                "exact_match": 2,
                "class": 2
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 19800,
                "question": "when he's asleep are his powers transferred as well?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "101:132,35:78,95:101|20:78|101:132,20:78,95:101|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"20:78\": 1, \"35:78\": 1, \"bad_question\": 1}",
                "para_text": "Snow told reporters he had a chemo session scheduled later Friday.  Watch Snow talk about Bush's procedure and his own colon cancer Â»\n\n\"The president wants to encourage everybody to use surveillance,\" Snow said.\n\nThe American Cancer Society recommends that people without high-risk factors or symptoms begin getting screened for signs of colorectal cancer at age 50. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "",
                "exact_match": 2,
                "class": 2
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 23035,
                "question": "is bush's colon healthy?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "401:430|446:521|362:397,401:430|401:430",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"401:430\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "no abnormalities were found",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 26479,
                "question": "What problems were found in 2002 exam?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "401:418|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"401:418\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "no abnormalities",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 39270,
                "question": "Who will have a routine colonoscopy?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "101:116|101:116",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "president bush",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 39663,
                "question": "Who will his powers be transferred to?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "35:47|20:47|20:47",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The procedure will be supervised by Dr. Richard Tubb and conducted by a multidisciplinary team from the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nA colonoscopy is the most sensitive test for colon cancer, rectal cancer and polyps, small clumps of cells that can become cancerous, according to the Mayo Clinic. Small polyps may be removed during the procedure.\n\nSnow said that was the case when Bush had colonoscopies before becoming president.",
                "pred_ans": "bush",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 47538,
                "question": "What procedure is President Bush having?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|146:159",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"146:159\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "colonoscopy",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 48573,
                "question": "What will President Bush have on Saturday?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "138:159|119:159|136:159|136:159",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"136:159\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "a routine colonoscopy",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 52927,
                "question": "What will President Bush have?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "138:159|146:159|138:159",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "a routine colonoscopy",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 54765,
                "question": "Who had a colonoscopy in 2002?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|101:116|101:146",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.333333333333,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"101:146\": 1, \"101:116\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "president bush",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 61334,
                "question": "What was the date in 2002 when Bush had his last colonoscopy, which found no problems?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "386:391|386:391",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "june",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 76023,
                "question": "What procedure is he having?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "138:159|146:159|138:159",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "colonoscopy",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 79888,
                "question": "What happens to his powers while he is anesthetized?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "20:78|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"20:78\": 2, \"none\": 1}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "vice president dick cheney will serve as acting president briefly saturday",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 83456,
                "question": "When did he last have this procedure?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "386:397|386:397",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "june 2002",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 85485,
                "question": "Who will be in charge while he's undergoing the procedure?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "35:47|20:47|20:47",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The procedure will be supervised by Dr. Richard Tubb and conducted by a multidisciplinary team from the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nA colonoscopy is the most sensitive test for colon cancer, rectal cancer and polyps, small clumps of cells that can become cancerous, according to the Mayo Clinic. Small polyps may be removed during the procedure.\n\nSnow said that was the case when Bush had colonoscopies before becoming president.",
                "pred_ans": "dr . richard tubb",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 87139,
                "question": "Who will be granted presidential power while Bush is anesthetized?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "20:47|20:47,52:78|101:111,20:47,52:95|20:47,52:78",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"20:47\": 2}",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "vice president dick cheney",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 95196,
                "question": "What is the reason why the President's powers will be transferred to the vice president?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "119:159|138:159|111:116,119:159|119:159",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"119:159\": 2, \"138:159\": 1}",
                "para_text": "The procedure will be supervised by Dr. Richard Tubb and conducted by a multidisciplinary team from the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nA colonoscopy is the most sensitive test for colon cancer, rectal cancer and polyps, small clumps of cells that can become cancerous, according to the Mayo Clinic. Small polyps may be removed during the procedure.\n\nSnow said that was the case when Bush had colonoscopies before becoming president.",
                "pred_ans": "small polyps may be removed during the procedure . snow said that was the case when bush had colonoscopies",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 95406,
                "question": "who will have the president's powers when he is anesthetized?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "35:47|20:25,35:47|20:25,35:47",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "vice president dick cheney",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 97216,
                "question": "think there will be problems now?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The procedure will be supervised by Dr. Richard Tubb and conducted by a multidisciplinary team from the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nA colonoscopy is the most sensitive test for colon cancer, rectal cancer and polyps, small clumps of cells that can become cancerous, according to the Mayo Clinic. Small polyps may be removed during the procedure.\n\nSnow said that was the case when Bush had colonoscopies before becoming president.",
                "pred_ans": "snow said that was the case when bush had colonoscopies before becoming president .",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 97338,
                "question": "What medical procedure will Bush have on Saturday?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "138:159|138:159",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "colonoscopy",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 101836,
                "question": "When was Bush's last colonoscopy?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "386:397|386:397",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "june 2002",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 103684,
                "question": "What person  will be presidentwhen Bush is anesthtized?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "20:47|35:47|None|20:47",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"20:47\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The procedure will be supervised by Dr. Richard Tubb and conducted by a multidisciplinary team from the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nA colonoscopy is the most sensitive test for colon cancer, rectal cancer and polyps, small clumps of cells that can become cancerous, according to the Mayo Clinic. Small polyps may be removed during the procedure.\n\nSnow said that was the case when Bush had colonoscopies before becoming president.",
                "pred_ans": "bush had colonoscopies before becoming president",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 110474,
                "question": "Who is in charge while the president is anesthetized?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "20:25,35:47|111:116,20:25,35:68,78:95|111:116,20:25,35:68,78:95",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "dick cheney",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 112770,
                "question": "What is the date of the Saturday that President Bush will have a routine colonoscopy?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "WASHINGTON (CNN) -- Vice President Dick Cheney will serve as acting president briefly Saturday while President Bush is anesthetized for a routine colonoscopy, White House spokesman Tony Snow said Friday.\n\nBush is scheduled to have the medical procedure, expected to take about 2 1/2 hours, at the presidential retreat at Camp David, Maryland, Snow said.\n\nBush's last colonoscopy was in June 2002, and no abnormalities were found, Snow said.",
                "pred_ans": "friday",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "story_id": "./cnn/stories/2ad31cae96512af5105b9b23f9b681dc732b2605.story",
        "story_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.\n\n\"We had quite a spike in calls, mostly calls of inquiry, none of any injury, none of any damage that was reported,\" said Capt. Al Casciato of the San Francisco police. \"It was fairly mild.\"  Watch police describe concerned calls immediately after the quake Â»\n\nThe quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
        "questions": [
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 3697,
                "question": "what are 2000 customers without?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "214:221|214:221",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "power",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 3804,
                "question": "What number of customers are without electricity",
                "answer_char_ranges": "190:196|190:196",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "people ' s homes",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 4648,
                "question": "where was it centered?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "700:737|700:725|694:737|694:737",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"694:737\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "about two miles east - northeast of oakland",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 9591,
                "question": "What was the magnitude of the Oakland quake",
                "answer_char_ranges": "48:52|48:52",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "4 . 2",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 19972,
                "question": "what was the magnitude of the earthquake?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "48:52|48:52",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "4 . 2",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 25274,
                "question": "What did the power company say?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "169:214|169:214",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "the quake left about 2 , 000 customers without power",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 28027,
                "question": "Where was the epicenter of the earthquake?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "700:737|694:737|None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"694:737\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "oakland",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 28974,
                "question": "What magnitude was the quake",
                "answer_char_ranges": "48:52|48:52",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "4 . 2",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 38674,
                "question": "What is the number of customers without electricity?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|184:196",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"184:196\": 2}",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "2 , 000",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 46675,
                "question": "where is oakland?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "788:842|788:842",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "just east of san francisco",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 46684,
                "question": "what did power company say?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "169:214|169:214",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "the quake left about 2 , 000 customers without power",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 56824,
                "question": "Where was the epicenter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "685:762|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"685:762\": 2, \"none\": 1}",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "oakland",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 58248,
                "question": "What did the earthquake do?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "169:221,891:925|379:410,63:92|63:92|63:99",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"63:92\": 1, \"169:221\": 2}",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "left about 2 , 000 customers without power",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 58811,
                "question": "Where was the quake?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "73:87|73:92|694:737|73:92",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"694:737\": 1, \"73:92\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "about two miles east - northeast of oakland",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 60085,
                "question": "What caused the power outage?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "169:179|173:214|36:63|36:63",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"36:63\": 2}",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "a magnitude 4 . 2 earthquake",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 69102,
                "question": "What did the police say?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "411:527,843:854,861:925|411:527,579:601|411:571|427:443,881:925",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"411:571\": 1, \"411:527\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "the quake set off alarms at people ' s homes",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 81173,
                "question": "What number of electricity customers were affected by the power outage?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "190:196|184:196|169:196,206:214|190:196",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"184:196\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "3 . 6 miles",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 81206,
                "question": "We're there any injuries",
                "answer_char_ranges": "468:476,480:488|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"468:476\": 2, \"bad_question\": 1}",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "the quake left about 2 , 000 customers without power",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 81767,
                "question": "where was it centred?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "700:737|685:694,700:737|694:762|671:681,685:762",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"694:762\": 2, \"700:737\": 1}",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "san francisco , california",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 89742,
                "question": "Were there any reports of damage or injury",
                "answer_char_ranges": "443:476,488:496,507:527|468:476,488:496|427:443|468:476,488:496",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "according to the usgs , magnitude 4 . 2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 89960,
                "question": "Who was injured?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "468:488|468:473|None|468:488",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "chad myers",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 92881,
                "question": "What set off home alarms?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "881:891,906:918|48:63|881:891|885:891",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"48:63\": 1, \"885:891\": 1, \"881:891\": 1}",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "the quake",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 98096,
                "question": "Where was the epi-center of the earthquake?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "685:737|700:737|0:15|694:762",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"700:737\": 1, \"685:737\": 1, \"694:762\": 1}",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "about two miles east - northeast of oakland",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 100955,
                "question": "What was the size of the earthquake?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "38:52|38:52",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "magnitude 4 . 2",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 105686,
                "question": "What was the magnitude measured at?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "48:52|48:52",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "The quake was centered about two miles east-northeast of Oakland, at a depth of 3.6 miles, the USGS said. Oakland is just east of San Francisco, across San Francisco Bay.\n\nAn Oakland police dispatcher told CNN the quake set off alarms at people's homes. The shaking lasted about 50 seconds, said CNN meteorologist Chad Myers.\n\nAccording to the USGS, magnitude 4.2 quakes are felt indoors and may break dishes and windows and overturn unstable objects. Pendulum clocks may stop. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "4 . 2",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 117615,
                "question": "What did the power company announce?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|173:214",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2, \"173:214\": 1}",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "the quake left about 2 , 000 customers without power",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 118430,
                "question": "Are many customers without power",
                "answer_char_ranges": "190:196|190:196",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "SAN FRANCISCO, California (CNN)  -- A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook the San Francisco area Friday at 4:42 a.m. PT (7:42 a.m. ET), the U.S. Geological Survey reported.\n\nThe quake left about 2,000 customers without power, said David Eisenhower, a spokesman for Pacific Gas and Light.\n\nUnder the USGS classification, a magnitude 4.2 earthquake is considered \"light,\" which it says usually causes minimal damage.",
                "pred_ans": "the quake left about 2 , 000 customers without power",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "story_id": "./cnn/stories/cbd21ed724b7e4a075ab4ae9a45d9e86d6151283.story",
        "story_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:\n\nChairman [Henry] Waxman, [D-California], Congressman [Thomas] Davis, [R-Virginia], members of the committee, my name is Eric Prince, and I am the chairman and CEO of the Prince Group and Blackwater USA.\n\nBlackwater's a team of dedicated professionals who provide training to America's military and law enforcement communities and risk their lives to protect Americans in harm's way overseas.\n\nUnder the direction and oversight of the United States government, Blackwater provides an opportunity for military and law enforcement veterans with a record of honorable service to continue their support to the United States.\n\nWords alone cannot express the respect I have for these brave men and women who defend -- who volunteer to defend U.S. personnel facilities and diplomatic missions. I am proud to be there to represent them today.\n\nAfter almost five years in active service as a U.S. Navy SEAL, I founded Blackwater in 1997. I wanted to offer the military and law enforcement communities assistance by providing expert instruction and world-class training venues. Ten years later, Blackwater trains approximately 500 members of the United States military and law enforcement agencies every day.\n\nAfter 9/11, when the U.S. began its stabilization efforts in Afghanistan and then Iraq, the United States government called upon Blackwater to fill a need for protective services in hostile areas. Blackwater responded immediately. We are extremely proud of answering that call in supporting our country.\n\nBlackwater personnel supporting our overseas missions are all military and law enforcement veterans, many of whom have recent military deployments. No individual ever protected by Blackwater has ever been killed or seriously injured. There is no better evidence of the skill and dedication of these men.\n\nAt the same time, 30 brave men have made the ultimate sacrifice while working for Blackwater and its affiliates. Numerous others have been wounded and permanently maimed. The entire Blackwater family mourns the loss of these brave lives. Our thoughts and our prayers are with their families.\n\nThe areas of Iraq in which we operate are particularly dangerous and challenging. Blackwater personnel are subject to regular attacks by terrorists and other nefarious forces within Iraq. We're the targets of the same ruthless enemies that have killed more than 3,800 American military personnel and thousands of innocent Iraqis.\n\nAny incident where Americans are attacked serves as a reminder of the hostile environment in which our professionals work to keep American officials and dignitaries safe, including visiting members of Congress.\n\nIn doing so, more American service members are available to fight the enemy.\n\nBlackwater shares the committee's interest in ensuring the accountability and oversight of contract personnel supporting U.S. operations.\n\nThe company's personnel are already accountable under and subject to numerous statutes, treaties and regulations of the United States. Blackwater looks forward to working with Congress and the executive branch to ensure that any necessary improvements to these laws and policies are implemented.\n\nThe worldwide personnel protection services contract, which has been provided to this committee, was competitively awarded and details almost every aspect of operation and contract performance, including the hiring, vetting guidelines, background checks, screening, training standards, rules of force and conduct standards.\n\nIn Iraq, Blackwater reports to the embassy's regional security officer, or RSO. All Blackwater movements and operations are directed by the RSO. In conjunction with internal company procedures and controls, the RSO ensures that Blackwater complies with all relevant contractual terms and conditions, as well as any applicable laws and regulations.\n\nWe have approximately 1,000 professionals serving today in Iraq as part of our nation's total force. Blackwater does not engage in offensive or military missions but performs only defensive security functions.\n\nMy understanding of the September 16 incident is that the Department of State and the FBI are conducting a full investigation, but those results are not yet available. We at Blackwater welcome the FBI review announced yesterday, and we will cooperate fully and look forward to receiving their conclusions.\n\nI just want to put some other things in perspective.\n\nA recent report from the Department of State stated that in 2007 Blackwater conducted 1,873 security details for diplomatic visits to the red zone, areas outside the Green Zone in Iraq, and there have been only 56 incidences in which weapons were discharged, or less than 3 percent of all movements.\n\nIn 2006, Blackwater conducted over 6,500 diplomatic movements in the Red Zone. Weapons were discharged in less than 1 percent of those missions.\n\nTo the extent there is any loss of innocent life, ever, let me be clear that I consider that tragic. Every life, whether American or Iraqi, is precious. I stress to the committee and to the American public, however, that I believe we acted appropriately at all times.\n\nI am prepared to answer your questions. E-mail to a friend",
        "questions": [
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 3871,
                "question": "Who acted appropriately at all times?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "In 2006, Blackwater conducted over 6,500 diplomatic movements in the Red Zone. Weapons were discharged in less than 1 percent of those missions.\n\nTo the extent there is any loss of innocent life, ever, let me be clear that I consider that tragic. Every life, whether American or Iraqi, is precious. I stress to the committee and to the American public, however, that I believe we acted appropriately at all times.\n\nI am prepared to answer your questions. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "the committee and to the american public",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 4508,
                "question": "Who testified before House panel?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "14:22,9:14|14:22,9:14",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "erik prince",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 8045,
                "question": "What involved Blackwater personnel?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "295:319,350:398|297:319|310:329|297:319",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"297:319\": 1, \"295:319\": 2}",
                "para_text": "The areas of Iraq in which we operate are particularly dangerous and challenging. Blackwater personnel are subject to regular attacks by terrorists and other nefarious forces within Iraq. We're the targets of the same ruthless enemies that have killed more than 3,800 American military personnel and thousands of innocent Iraqis.",
                "pred_ans": "regular attacks by terrorists and other nefarious forces within iraq",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 18460,
                "question": "who is CEO of Blackwater USA?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|14:22,9:14",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 1, \"14:22\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "erik prince",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 18833,
                "question": "What has prince said?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "566:582,590:627,634:660|457:466,474:482,498:510,519:526,540:574,577:582,594:620,623:627,634:640,644:660|412:428,437:456|594:627,634:660",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"594:627\": 1, \"437:456\": 1, \"594:620\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "opening statement",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 20117,
                "question": "What is name of CEO of Blackwater USA?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "14:22,9:14|14:22,9:14",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "erik prince",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 26331,
                "question": "who is probing a shootout?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "106:142,90:106|272:276|457:466,474:482|329:350",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 1, \"272:276\": 1, \"457:466\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "fbi",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 26803,
                "question": "Who said, \"I believe we acted appropriately at all times\"?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "14:22,9:14|143:192|14:62,9:14|143:156",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"143:156\": 2}",
                "para_text": "In 2006, Blackwater conducted over 6,500 diplomatic movements in the Red Zone. Weapons were discharged in less than 1 percent of those missions.\n\nTo the extent there is any loss of innocent life, ever, let me be clear that I consider that tragic. Every life, whether American or Iraqi, is precious. I stress to the committee and to the American public, however, that I believe we acted appropriately at all times.\n\nI am prepared to answer your questions. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "the committee",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 27092,
                "question": "who is prince testifying before?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "106:142,90:106|566:574,577:582,590:594,596:627,634:660|None|106:142,86:106",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"86:106\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "the house committee on oversight and government reform",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 34950,
                "question": "Who said they acted appropriately?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "143:156,5530:5532|5172:5183|143:156|4887:4907",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"143:156\": 2}",
                "para_text": "In 2006, Blackwater conducted over 6,500 diplomatic movements in the Red Zone. Weapons were discharged in less than 1 percent of those missions.\n\nTo the extent there is any loss of innocent life, ever, let me be clear that I consider that tragic. Every life, whether American or Iraqi, is precious. I stress to the committee and to the American public, however, that I believe we acted appropriately at all times.\n\nI am prepared to answer your questions. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "the committee and to the american public",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 37013,
                "question": "Which company was involved in shootout?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "329:340|297:310,319:350|46:62|329:350",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"46:62\": 1, \"329:340\": 1, \"329:350\": 1}",
                "para_text": "The areas of Iraq in which we operate are particularly dangerous and challenging. Blackwater personnel are subject to regular attacks by terrorists and other nefarious forces within Iraq. We're the targets of the same ruthless enemies that have killed more than 3,800 American military personnel and thousands of innocent Iraqis.",
                "pred_ans": "blackwater",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 39745,
                "question": "Who testified before the House panel?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "14:22,9:14|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"14:22\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "erik prince",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 43779,
                "question": "What was held amid an FBI probe into a shootout involving Blackwater personnel?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|106:142,90:106",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"90:106\": 3, \"none\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "the house committee on oversight and government reform",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 47482,
                "question": "Does Prince believe they acted appropriately?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "5530:5532,5540:5543,5563:5577|5530:5532,5540:5543,5563:5577",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "In 2006, Blackwater conducted over 6,500 diplomatic movements in the Red Zone. Weapons were discharged in less than 1 percent of those missions.\n\nTo the extent there is any loss of innocent life, ever, let me be clear that I consider that tragic. Every life, whether American or Iraqi, is precious. I stress to the committee and to the American public, however, that I believe we acted appropriately at all times.\n\nI am prepared to answer your questions. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "i stress to the committee and to the american public , however , that i believe we acted appropriately at all times",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 51905,
                "question": "Who is testifying before House panel?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "14:22,9:14|14:22,9:14",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "erik prince",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 59187,
                "question": "Were the actions appropriate?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "In 2006, Blackwater conducted over 6,500 diplomatic movements in the Red Zone. Weapons were discharged in less than 1 percent of those missions.\n\nTo the extent there is any loss of innocent life, ever, let me be clear that I consider that tragic. Every life, whether American or Iraqi, is precious. I stress to the committee and to the American public, however, that I believe we acted appropriately at all times.\n\nI am prepared to answer your questions. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "we acted appropriately at all times",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 64140,
                "question": "Who did the shootout involve?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "329:350|329:350",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Blackwater's a team of dedicated professionals who provide training to America's military and law enforcement communities and risk their lives to protect Americans in harm's way overseas.\n\nUnder the direction and oversight of the United States government, Blackwater provides an opportunity for military and law enforcement veterans with a record of honorable service to continue their support to the United States.",
                "pred_ans": "blackwater ' s a team of dedicated professionals who provide training to america ' s military and law enforcement communities and risk their lives to protect americans in harm ' s way overseas . under the direction and oversight of the united states government , blackwater provides an opportunity for military and law enforcement veterans",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 65377,
                "question": "Who is behind the probe?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "106:142,90:106|1078:1117,1119:1154,1158:1165,1172:1243|None|4887:4907",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.25,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"4887:4907\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Blackwater's a team of dedicated professionals who provide training to America's military and law enforcement communities and risk their lives to protect Americans in harm's way overseas.\n\nUnder the direction and oversight of the United States government, Blackwater provides an opportunity for military and law enforcement veterans with a record of honorable service to continue their support to the United States.",
                "pred_ans": "blackwater",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 68477,
                "question": "What company is prince the CEO of?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "46:62|46:62",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "blackwater usa",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 82686,
                "question": "Who was involved in the shootout?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "329:350|329:350",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "blackwater personnel",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 85328,
                "question": "Who is the CEO of Blackwater?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "14:22,26:35,57:62,9:14|14:22,9:14|14:22,9:14",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "erik prince",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 100574,
                "question": "Who thought Blackwater acted appropriately at all times?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "In 2006, Blackwater conducted over 6,500 diplomatic movements in the Red Zone. Weapons were discharged in less than 1 percent of those missions.\n\nTo the extent there is any loss of innocent life, ever, let me be clear that I consider that tragic. Every life, whether American or Iraqi, is precious. I stress to the committee and to the American public, however, that I believe we acted appropriately at all times.\n\nI am prepared to answer your questions. E-mail to a friend",
                "pred_ans": "the committee and to the american public",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 102280,
                "question": "Has Erik Prince testified yet?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "62:79|106:142,62:106|62:106|106:142,195:240,62:106",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"195:240\": 1, \"none\": 1, \"62:106\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "tuesday",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 105579,
                "question": "What was the FBI probe involving?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|295:319,329:398",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"295:319\": 2}",
                "para_text": "My understanding of the September 16 incident is that the Department of State and the FBI are conducting a full investigation, but those results are not yet available. We at Blackwater welcome the FBI review announced yesterday, and we will cooperate fully and look forward to receiving their conclusions.\n\nI just want to put some other things in perspective.",
                "pred_ans": "the department of state and the fbi are conducting a full investigation , but those results are not yet available",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 105888,
                "question": "Who held the hearings?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "106:142,90:106|217:240|217:231|106:142,90:106",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"90:106\": 2, \"217:231\": 1}",
                "para_text": "Blackwater's a team of dedicated professionals who provide training to America's military and law enforcement communities and risk their lives to protect Americans in harm's way overseas.\n\nUnder the direction and oversight of the United States government, Blackwater provides an opportunity for military and law enforcement veterans with a record of honorable service to continue their support to the United States.",
                "pred_ans": "the united states government",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 108209,
                "question": "Who did Prince testify before?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "106:142,90:106|106:142,86:106|106:142,90:106",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "the house committee on oversight and government reform",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 110001,
                "question": "Who testifies before House panel?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "14:22,26:62,9:14|14:62,9:14|143:156|14:22,9:14",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"143:156\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "erik prince",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 115895,
                "question": "Where did hearing happened?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|217:231",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"217:231\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- Erik Prince, the chairman and CEO of Blackwater USA, appeared Tuesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform.\n\nErik Prince, CEO and chairman of Blackwater USA, is sworn in Tuesday at a congressional hearing.\n\nThe committee convened amid an FBI investigation into a September 16 shootout involving Blackwater personnel that resulted in the deaths of Iraqi civilians.\n\nFollowing is a transcript of Prince's opening statement:",
                "pred_ans": "house committee on oversight and government reform",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "story_id": "./cnn/stories/e3dd06d326c8d53722bdc5c8428e29c68a60d0d5.story",
        "story_text": "(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family's \"lives were just changed forever\" by the tragedy.\n\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\n\n\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\" he said.\n\nAuman said the situation was \"hard to fathom.\"\n\n\"There's just no words to describe what we've been going through,\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \"We're numb, we're confused, we're heartbroken.\"\n\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\n\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.\n\nSix other South Carolina students were able to get out of the house in time. The six were treated and released from nearby Brunswick Community Hospital, but Auman's daughter was hospitalized again in Hartsville, South Carolina.\n\nAuthorities from the state Bureau of Investigation and the federal Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives are leading the investigation into the cause of the fire.\n\nOcean Isle Beach Mayor Debbie Smith said the house was \"engulfed\" in flames when the fire department arrived on the scene, about five minutes after being notified. The flames shot into the sky and ultimately left little more than portions of the framing.\n\nFire officials do not believe foul play was involved.  Watch a neighbor's video, fears of fast-burning fire Â»\n\nDennis A. Pruitt, the vice president for student affairs for the University of South Carolina, said investigators have said it would be Tuesday or Wednesday before the identities of the victims are confirmed publicly.\n\nIt could be as much as a month until investigators know the cause of the fire, Pruitt said.\n\nThe university did not cancel classes on Monday, but Pruitt said arrangements had been made for those who need to go home or stay out of class at the 28,000-student campus.\n\nPruitt said meetings had been held Sunday with members of Delta Delta Delta sorority and Sigma Alpha Epsilon fraternity. The South Carolina students were affiliated with those houses, he said, although he stressed that the weekend was not an official Greek function.\n\nHe also said counselors and ministers were available to help students deal with the loss of their classmates.\n\nThe university president, Dr. Andrew Sorenson, contacted the families of those who died in the fire to express the condolences and support of the university community.\n\nJay Laura, student president of the USC chapter of Sigma Alpha Epsilon, said the campus would pull together after the tragedy.\n\n\"If any place can come together to help in the healing process and the aftermath of an event like this, it is South Carolina,\" Laura said at a Monday afternoon press conference.\n\nFire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\n\n\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.\n\n\"The smoke was pouring out, couldn't really breathe, so I had to make a quick decision. [I] just kind of leaned out the window and luckily I jumped far enough to make it into the canal.\"\n\nNeighbors flocked to see the fire as firefighters battled and ultimately got the blaze under control.  See the scenes of devastation Â»\n\nGeorge Smith, who lives across the street from the house, said he heard sirens between 6:30 and 7 a.m. and went outside to see \"the whole sky lit up.\"\n\n\"The whole house was completely engulfed in flames, up to about 20 feet,\" he said. \"I have never seen [a fire] move so fast.\"\n\nGeorge Smith said the house's occupants were \"partying in there yesterday and into the night.\" After about 10:30 p.m. Saturday they quieted down, he said.\n\nLinda Sing said she was walking her dog when she saw the fiery destruction. She noted that firefighters had saved an adjacent house by spraying it down with water.\n\n\"We knew there were people in there, but we hoped and prayed they'd gotten out,\" Sing said. \"This is the worst thing I've ever seen. We've had hurricanes, but this is worse.\"\n\nOcean Isle Beach is a popular resort destination along North Carolina's southern coast. The year-round population of the 7-mile-long island is about 425, but it swells to about 25,000 during the summer season, according to the town's Web site. E-mail to a friend",
        "questions": [
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 2116,
                "question": "Who mourns deaths of six students?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "13:51,736:765,9:13|736:757|736:757",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"There's just no words to describe what we've been going through,\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \"We're numb, we're confused, we're heartbroken.\"\n\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\n\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.",
                "pred_ans": "two college campuses",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 5265,
                "question": "Whose daughter was hospitalized?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "184:195|184:195",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family's \"lives were just changed forever\" by the tragedy.\n\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\n\n\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\" he said.",
                "pred_ans": "chip auman",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 9463,
                "question": "From which university were the six dead students?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "789:807|792:798,822:830|789:807",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "He also said counselors and ministers were available to help students deal with the loss of their classmates.\n\nThe university president, Dr. Andrew Sorenson, contacted the families of those who died in the fire to express the condolences and support of the university community.\n\nJay Laura, student president of the USC chapter of Sigma Alpha Epsilon, said the campus would pull together after the tragedy.",
                "pred_ans": "usc",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 10651,
                "question": "What happened to the house owner's daughter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "247:264|225:288|225:336|225:264",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"225:264\": 2, \"225:288\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family's \"lives were just changed forever\" by the tragedy.\n\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\n\n\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\" he said.",
                "pred_ans": "hospitalized and in stable condition",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 10773,
                "question": "University of South Carolina mourns deaths of six students",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 1.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"There's just no words to describe what we've been going through,\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \"We're numb, we're confused, we're heartbroken.\"\n\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\n\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.",
                "pred_ans": "six university of south carolina students and a clemson university student died in the fire early sunday morning in ocean isle beach , north carolina .",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 16309,
                "question": "What story did the survivor jump from?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "3131:3150|3131:3143|3131:3143",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\n\n\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.",
                "pred_ans": "third - story window",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 19634,
                "question": "Who mourns the students?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|13:19,184:195,19:51,9:13",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 2, \"184:195\": 2}",
                "para_text": "He also said counselors and ministers were available to help students deal with the loss of their classmates.\n\nThe university president, Dr. Andrew Sorenson, contacted the families of those who died in the fire to express the condolences and support of the university community.\n\nJay Laura, student president of the USC chapter of Sigma Alpha Epsilon, said the campus would pull together after the tragedy.",
                "pred_ans": "the university community",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 24054,
                "question": "Who mourned the deaths?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "736:757|736:757",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "He also said counselors and ministers were available to help students deal with the loss of their classmates.\n\nThe university president, Dr. Andrew Sorenson, contacted the families of those who died in the fire to express the condolences and support of the university community.\n\nJay Laura, student president of the USC chapter of Sigma Alpha Epsilon, said the campus would pull together after the tragedy.",
                "pred_ans": "the university community",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 25785,
                "question": "which was the cause of death of the 6 students?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "98:103|861:866|861:866",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Authorities from the state Bureau of Investigation and the federal Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives are leading the investigation into the cause of the fire.\n\nOcean Isle Beach Mayor Debbie Smith said the house was \"engulfed\" in flames when the fire department arrived on the scene, about five minutes after being notified. The flames shot into the sky and ultimately left little more than portions of the framing.",
                "pred_ans": "fire",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 33660,
                "question": "What school did the students go to?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "778:807,822:841|792:807,822:841|778:807,816:820,822:841|778:807,822:841",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"778:807\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Dennis A. Pruitt, the vice president for student affairs for the University of South Carolina, said investigators have said it would be Tuesday or Wednesday before the identities of the victims are confirmed publicly.\n\nIt could be as much as a month until investigators know the cause of the fire, Pruitt said.\n\nThe university did not cancel classes on Monday, but Pruitt said arrangements had been made for those who need to go home or stay out of class at the 28,000-student campus.",
                "pred_ans": "university of south carolina",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 38926,
                "question": "What number of survivors were hospitalized?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|1002:1010,1015:1078",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1002:1010\": 2}",
                "para_text": "\"There's just no words to describe what we've been going through,\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \"We're numb, we're confused, we're heartbroken.\"\n\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\n\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.",
                "pred_ans": "six",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 42415,
                "question": "What did the University mourn?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "57:85|2637:2664|57:80|774:778,789:830,841:866",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"57:85\": 1, \"57:80\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Dennis A. Pruitt, the vice president for student affairs for the University of South Carolina, said investigators have said it would be Tuesday or Wednesday before the identities of the victims are confirmed publicly.\n\nIt could be as much as a month until investigators know the cause of the fire, Pruitt said.\n\nThe university did not cancel classes on Monday, but Pruitt said arrangements had been made for those who need to go home or stay out of class at the 28,000-student campus.",
                "pred_ans": "fire",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 43922,
                "question": "Who was hospitalized?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "184:195,204:225|184:225|1082:1099,204:225|184:195,204:225",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1082:1099\": 1, \"184:225\": 1, \"204:225\": 1}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family's \"lives were just changed forever\" by the tragedy.\n\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\n\n\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\" he said.",
                "pred_ans": "his 18 - year - old daughter",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 44432,
                "question": "because I try out a survivor?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "3040:3045|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"bad_question\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\n\n\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.",
                "pred_ans": "jumped out of a third - story window into a canal to escape the flames",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 46077,
                "question": "Where did one survivor jump?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "3107:3235|3131:3163|3122:3163|3122:3163",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"3122:3163\": 1, \"none\": 1, \"3131:3163\": 1}",
                "para_text": "Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\n\n\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.",
                "pred_ans": "a canal",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 47093,
                "question": "What was the house owner's daughter?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "204:216|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"204:216\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family's \"lives were just changed forever\" by the tragedy.\n\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\n\n\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\" he said.",
                "pred_ans": "18 - year - old",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 57743,
                "question": "who jum p imto a canal to escape?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "3054:3067|3054:3067",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\n\n\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.",
                "pred_ans": "tripp wylie",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 61251,
                "question": "Who mourns death of six students?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "184:195|736:757|736:765|929:935",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"736:765\": 1, \"184:195\": 1, \"736:757\": 1}",
                "para_text": "\"There's just no words to describe what we've been going through,\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \"We're numb, we're confused, we're heartbroken.\"\n\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\n\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.",
                "pred_ans": "two college campuses",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 64978,
                "question": "One survivor jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape",
                "answer_char_ranges": "3054:3067|3060:3067,3069:3107|238:243,98:103|1082:1099",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"bad_question\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\n\n\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.",
                "pred_ans": "tripp wylie",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 65887,
                "question": "what was the amount of suvivors?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|925:929",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"925:929\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Authorities from the state Bureau of Investigation and the federal Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives are leading the investigation into the cause of the fire.\n\nOcean Isle Beach Mayor Debbie Smith said the house was \"engulfed\" in flames when the fire department arrived on the scene, about five minutes after being notified. The flames shot into the sky and ultimately left little more than portions of the framing.",
                "pred_ans": "five",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 68669,
                "question": "\"Heartbroken\" house owner's daughter among six survivors hospitalized",
                "answer_char_ranges": "None|225:238,243:247",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 1, \"bad_question\": 2}",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family's \"lives were just changed forever\" by the tragedy.\n\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\n\n\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\" he said.",
                "pred_ans": "chip auman said his 18 - year - old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 71495,
                "question": "What was the number of survivors hospitalized?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1006:1010|1002:1078,925:1002|1006:1010,1015:1023,1027:1036,1068:1078,925:929,950:1002|57:63",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"1006:1010\": 2, \"925:929\": 1}",
                "para_text": "Authorities from the state Bureau of Investigation and the federal Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives are leading the investigation into the cause of the fire.\n\nOcean Isle Beach Mayor Debbie Smith said the house was \"engulfed\" in flames when the fire department arrived on the scene, about five minutes after being notified. The flames shot into the sky and ultimately left little more than portions of the framing.",
                "pred_ans": "five",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 78890,
                "question": "Where did the man jump into?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "3126:3150,3155:3163|3157:3163|3155:3163|3155:3163",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"none\": 1, \"3155:3163\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Authorities from the state Bureau of Investigation and the federal Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives are leading the investigation into the cause of the fire.\n\nOcean Isle Beach Mayor Debbie Smith said the house was \"engulfed\" in flames when the fire department arrived on the scene, about five minutes after being notified. The flames shot into the sky and ultimately left little more than portions of the framing.",
                "pred_ans": "the sky",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 86822,
                "question": "Where did the survivor land when escaping?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "3131:3150|3549:3566|3157:3163|3157:3163",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"3549:3566\": 2}",
                "para_text": "Authorities from the state Bureau of Investigation and the federal Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives are leading the investigation into the cause of the fire.\n\nOcean Isle Beach Mayor Debbie Smith said the house was \"engulfed\" in flames when the fire department arrived on the scene, about five minutes after being notified. The flames shot into the sky and ultimately left little more than portions of the framing.",
                "pred_ans": "ocean isle beach",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 90415,
                "question": "Who  among six survivors hospitalized?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "184:225|None",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.5,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "{\"184:225\": 2}",
                "para_text": "\"There's just no words to describe what we've been going through,\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \"We're numb, we're confused, we're heartbroken.\"\n\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\n\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.",
                "pred_ans": "university of south carolina students and a clemson university student",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 90721,
                "question": "Who  jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "3054:3067|3054:3067",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\n\n\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.",
                "pred_ans": "tripp wylie",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 92373,
                "question": "Who jumped in a canal?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "3054:3067|3054:3067",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\n\n\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.",
                "pred_ans": "tripp wylie",
                "exact_match": 1,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 103869,
                "question": "where they are hospitalized survivors?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "1125:1153|1048:1078|1125:1153",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "(CNN) -- The owner of a North Carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said Monday that his family's \"lives were just changed forever\" by the tragedy.\n\nChip Auman said his 18-year-old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition because of complications from smoke inhalation.\n\n\"The thought of losing a child is unimaginable to me, and as a father my heart goes out to the families that lost a loved one in this situation,\" he said.",
                "pred_ans": "north carolina beach house where seven college students died in a weekend fire said monday that his family ' s \" lives were just changed forever \" by the tragedy . chip auman said his 18 - year - old daughter survived the fire but was hospitalized and in stable condition",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 0
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 111251,
                "question": "Where did one survivor jump to?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "3150:3163|3558:3566|3150:3163",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "Fire survivor Tripp Wylie, a 20-year-old South Carolina sophomore, said he jumped out of a third-story window into a canal to escape the flames and was unable to get back in to help his friends.\n\n\"I could see a buddy of mine off to the left who had gotten out. He was just yelling at me to jump and stuff,\" Wylie told CNN affiliate WYFF.",
                "pred_ans": "a canal",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            },
            {
                "Unnamed: 0": 115491,
                "question": "which university mourns deaths of six students?",
                "answer_char_ranges": "789:807|792:807,822:830|789:807",
                "is_answer_absent": 0.0,
                "is_question_bad": "?",
                "validated_answers": "",
                "para_text": "\"There's just no words to describe what we've been going through,\" he said, asking for prayers for survivors and the families of those who died. \"We're numb, we're confused, we're heartbroken.\"\n\nTwo college campuses mourned Monday.\n\nSix University of South Carolina students and a Clemson University student died in the fire early Sunday morning in Ocean Isle Beach, North Carolina.",
                "pred_ans": "university of south carolina",
                "exact_match": 0,
                "class": 1
            }
        ]
    }
]
